Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations: an inventory
Harvard College Observatory observations, logs, instrument readings, and calculations
- Gould's Universal Index, KG11365.253 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: M3.
- [Tables, Procedures], KG11365.254 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: M5.
- Table of Contents of various books containing records of observations, 1841 to 1855; KG11365.255 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: M6.
- Various memoranda [Longitude determination, mag. Measure, etc.], 1844 to 1855; KG11365.256 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: M7.
- Catalog Stars, 1854 to 1858; KG11365.257 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: M9.
- Tables for apportioning Instrumental Corrections, 1855; KG11365.258 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: M10.
- Catalogue of Stars for Zones, 1853; KG11365.259 (Box 6)
  Also identified as: M11.
- Reduction of Stars from 0 to 1 degrees, 1853; KG11365.260 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: M12.
- Printing of Zone Observations & History and Description of the Observatory, 1854; KG11365.261 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: M13.
- Lists of persons and Institution recipients of HCO Annals, KG11365.262 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: M14.
- Meteorological, 1861-01-01 to 1863-05-01; KG11365.263 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: M15.
- 1859-60 Comet Seeker, 1859-12-01 to 1860-09-11; KG11365.264 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: M16.
- Colorado Survey - Time, 1857-12-13 to 1858-05-23; KG11365.265 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: M17.
- Colorado Survey - Latitude by Polaris, 1857-12-13 to 1858-05-23; KG11365.266 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: M18.
- [Solar Observations], 1855-01-05 to 1855-05-02; KG11365.267 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: M19.
- [Catalog of Bright Nebulae and Clusters], 1850-06-16 to 1853-05-01; KG11365.268 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: M20.
- [Comet Seeking], 1847-06-10 to 1850-06-05; KG11365.269 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: M21.
- Books received at the Observatory of Harvard College, 1862 to 1867; KG11365.270 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: M23.
- Reductions of Moon Culminations, 1849-01-01 to 1852-05-28; KG11365.271 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: M24.
- Reductions of Moon Culminations, 1851-07-01 to 1854-10-02; KG11365.272 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: M25.
- P.S.N [drawings of star configuration and angles], 1856-06-16 to 1856-07-04; KG11365.273 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: M26.
- P.S.N [drawings of star configuration and angles], 1850-11-15 to 1851-08-22; KG11365.274 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: M27.
- Gould's Universal Index, KG11365.275 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: M28.
- Printing, KG11365.276 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: M29.
- Memoranda for Observatory Report, 1861-01-07 to 1864-12-31; KG11365.277 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: M30.
- Memoranda, 1862-01-03 to 1865-01-02; KG11365.278 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: M31.
- Catalog of Books in the Phillips Library, commenced, 1856-10-09; KG11365.279 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: M32.
- Chronometer - Stars, 1862 to 1865; KG11365.280 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: M33.
- Transit Catalog, KG11365.281 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: M34.
- Eclipse of 4/25/1864 - Portland, KG11365.282 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: M35.
- Account of Various Records and Papers belonging to the Observatory, 1866; KG11365.283 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: M36.
- Equatorial, 1866-06-09 to 1866-07-09; KG11365.284 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: N1.
- Equatorial, 1866-07-09 to 1866-07-24; KG11365.285 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: N2.
- Equatorial, 1866-07-24 to 1866-08-13; KG11365.286 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: N3.
- Equatorial, 1866-08-13 to 1866-08-26; KG11365.287 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: N4.
- Equatorial, 1866-08-26 to 1866-09-12; KG11365.288 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: N5.
- Equatorial, 1866-09-12 to 1866-10-02; KG11365.289 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: N6.
- Equatorial, 1866-10-02 to 1866-10-22; KG11365.290 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: N7.
- Equatorial, 1866-10-22 to 1867-01-23; KG11365.291 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: N8.
- Equatorial, 1867-01-23 to 1867-04-25; KG11365.292 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: N9.
- Equatorial, 1867-04-25 to 1867-10-25; KG11365.293 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: N10.
- Equatorial, 1867-10-25 to 1868-01-27; KG11365.294 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: N11.
- Equatorial, 1868-01-27 to 1868-04-01; KG11365.295 (Box 7)
  Also identified as: N12.
- Equatorial [Spectra], 1868-04-01 to 1868-10-10; KG11365.296 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N13.
- Equatorial, 1868-10-10 to 1868-12-22; KG11365.297 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N14.
- Equatorial, 1868-12-22 to 1869-04-28; KG11365.298 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N15.
- Equatorial, 1869-04-28 to 1869-10-14; KG11365.299 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N16.
- Equatorial, 1869-10-14 to 1871-10-31; KG11365.300 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N17.
- Equatorial Miscellaneous Observations, 1871-10-31 to 1869-12-24; KG11365.301 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N18.
- Equatorial Miscellaneous Observations, 1869-12-24 to 1874-12-08; KG11365.302 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N19.
- Equatorial Miscellaneous Observations, 1874-12-08 to 1870-07-13; KG11365.303 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N20.
- Asteroids, 1870-07-13 to 1871-02-13; KG11365.304 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N21.
- Asteroids, 1871-02-13 to 1871-08-10; KG11365.305 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N22.
- Asteroids, KG11365.306 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N23.
  W.A. Rogers.
- Asteroids, KG11365.307 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N24.
- Reduction of Asteroid Observations, 1870; KG11365.308 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N25.
- Reduction of Asteroid Observations, 1870 to 1871; KG11365.309 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N26.
- Reduction to apparent place of some stars used in 1870, KG11365.310 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N27.
- Reduction to apparent place of some stars used in 1870, KG11365.311 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N28.
- Reduction of Asteroid Observations, 1870; KG11365.312 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N29.
- Search for Asteroids, 1870; KG11365.313 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N30.
- Equatorial - observations of asteroids and comets, KG11365.314 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N31.
- Computation of apparent place and differentiated refraction, 1866-06-30 to 1866-04-26; KG11365.315 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N32.
- Reduction of Equatorial Observations, 1866-10-15 to 1866-08-26; KG11365.316 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N33.
- Equatorial (copy), 1866-04-09 to 1866-08-26; KG11365.317 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N34.
- Equatorial (copy), 1866-08-27 to 1866-10-21; KG11365.318 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N35.
- Equatorial (copy), 1866-10-21 to 1867-01-14; KG11365.319 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N36.
- Equatorial (copy), 1867-01-14 to 1867-04-26; KG11365.320 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N37.
- Equatorial (copy), 1867-04-26 to 1867-10-22; KG11365.321 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N38.
- Equatorial (copy), 1867-10-22 to 1868-02-03; KG11365.322 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N39.
- Equatorial (copy), 1868-02-03 to 1868-06-28; KG11365.323 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N40.
- Catalog of Nebulae, KG11365.324 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N41.
- Measurement of photographs of eclipse, 1869 to 1870; KG11365.325 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N42.
- Measurement of photographs of solar eclipse, 1870; KG11365.326 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N43.
- Notes to sketches of sun by E.L. Trouvelot, 1870-10-30 to 1873-04-14; KG11365.327 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N44.
- Notes to sketches of sun by E.L. Trouvelot, 1873-04-14 to 1874-09-30; KG11365.328 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N45.
- Solar Photography, 1870-07-04 to 1876-11-30; KG11365.329 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N46.
- General Record of Work, 1869 to 1872; KG11365.329a
  Also identified as: N48.
- Tables, etc., 1866 to 1867; KG11365.330 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N50.
- Reduced Measures of Double Stars - Equatorial, 1866 to 1867; KG11365.331 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: N51.
- East Transit Observations, 1866-05-01 to 1866-09-04; KG11365.332 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: O1.
- East Transit Observations, 1866-09-04 to 1867-05-31; KG11365.333 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: O2.
- East Transit Observations, 1867-05-31 to 1867-11-09; KG11365.334 (Box 8)
  Also identified as: O3.
- East Transit Observations, 1867-11-09 to 1868-07-16; KG11365.335 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O4.
- East Transit Observations, 1868-07-16 to 1868-10-03; KG11365.336 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O5.
- East Transit Observations (time), 1868-10-03 to 1869-08-29; KG11365.337 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O6.
- East Transit Observations (time), 1869-08-29 to 1870-06-12; KG11365.338 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O7.
- East Transit Observations (Occultations), 1870-06-12 to 1871-12-01; KG11365.339 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O8.
- East Transit Observations (time), 1871-12-01 to 1871-12-27; KG11365.340 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O9.
- Chronograph Record, 1866-04-02 to 1869-07-29; KG11365.341 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O10.
- East Transit (errors), 1866-04-17 to 1867-09-17; KG11365.342 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O11.
- Longitude Campaign: Cambridge - Washington, 1867; KG11365.343 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O12.
- Transit Observations, 1867-06-28 to 1867-06-29; KG11365.344 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O13.
- Formulae for Reduction of Transit Observations and Tables, 1867; KG11365.345 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O14.
- Chronograph Record, 1867-07-31 to 1867-12-19; KG11365.346 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O15.
- Chronograph Record, 1867-12-19 to 1868-08-04; KG11365.347 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O16.
- Chronograph Record, 1868-08-04 to 1869-08-13; KG11365.348 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O17.
- Chronograph Record, 1869-08-13 to 1870-07-07; KG11365.349 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O18.
- Record of Errors of Clocks, 1866 to 1869; KG11365.350 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O19.
- Stars to be observed with East Transit, 1868 to 1870; KG11365.351 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O20?.
- Second Computation of Instrument Errors, 1867 to 1868; KG11365.352 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O20.
- Longitudes Computations from Coast Survey, 1869; KG11365.353 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O21.
- [Transit Observations], 1870-08-24 to 1870-10-23; KG11365.354 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O22.
- Longitude - Field Reductions, 1871; KG11365.355 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O23.
- Clock Corrections, 1869 to 1872; KG11365.356 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O24.
- Clock Corrections, 1872 to 1875; KG11365.357 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O25.
- Clock Corrections, 1875; KG11365.358 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O26.
- Notes on Astronomy Engravings, Spanish Weather Record, Phillips Fund, KG11365.359 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O27.
- Eclipse of 1869, Reports, KG11365.360 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O28.
- Personal equation observations, 1871; KG11365.361 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: O29.
- Magnetic Observations, 1866-08-16 to 1868-02-17; KG11365.362 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: P1.
- Meteorological Observations, 1866; KG11365.363 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: P2.
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1866; KG11365.364 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: P3.
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1867; KG11365.365 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: P4.
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1868; KG11365.366 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: P5.
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1869; KG11365.367 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: P6.
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1870; KG11365.368 (Box 9)
  Also identified as: P7.
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1871; KG11365.369 (Box 10)
  Also identified as: P8.
  Clayton Octavo.
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1872; KG11365.370 (Box 10)
  Also identified as: P9.
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1873; KG11365.371 (Box 10)
  Also identified as: P10.
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1874; KG11365.372 (Box 10)
  Also identified as: P11.
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1875; KG11365.373 (Box 10)
  Also identified as: P12.
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1876; KG11365.374 (Box 10)
  Also identified as: P13.
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1877; KG11365.375 (Box 10)
  Also identified as: P14.
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1878; KG11365.376 (Box 10)
  Also identified as: P15.
- Daily Journal [meteorological], 1879; KG11365.377 (Box 10)
  Also identified as: P16.
- Meteorological Record of HCO, 1866 to 1868; KG11365.378 (Box 10)
  Also identified as: Q1.
- Meteorological Record of HCO, 1869; KG11365.379 (Box 10)
  Also identified as: Q2.
- Meteorological Record of HCO, 1870 to 1871; KG11365.380 (Box 10)
  Also identified as: Q3.
- Meteorological Record of HCO, 1872 to 1875; KG11365.381 (Box 10)
  Also identified as: Q4.
- Meteorological Record of HCO, 1866 to 1879; KG11365.382 (Box 10)
  Also identified as: Q5.
  Bulk of observations from 1878-1879.
- Mr. J.G. Homer's Original Minutes of Chronometer Expedition, 1857; KG11365.383 (Box 10)
- A___ A____ of the White Mts. Of New Hampshire (n.b. Annular Eclipse), 1853; KG11365.384 (Box 10)
- [Paris to Cambridge Telegraph], 1861; KG11365.385 (Box 10)
- U.S. Coast Survey, Benjamin Pierce, Subplot: Letter Book and Abstract - Long Party, 1868; KG11365.386 (Box 10)
- Observations and Longitude Computations (U.S. Coast Survey), 1872; KG11365.387 (Box 10)
- Longitude and Latitude no. 1 (Bolivia), 1892 to 1893; KG11365.388 (Box 10)
- Time Service, 1880-04-18 to 1881-04-19; KG11365.389 (Box 10)
- Meridian Circle Record - Mr. Austin, 1870-08-16 to 1871-05-13; KG11365.390 (Box 10)
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1872-03-06 to 1872-03-22; KG11365.391 (Box 10)
  Also identified as: Vol. 1.
  Charles S. Pierce.
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1872-03-22 to 1872-06-06; KG11365.392 (Box 10)
  Also identified as: Vol. 2.
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1872-06-06 to 1872-07-02; KG11365.393 (Box 10)
  Also identified as: Vol. 3.
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1872-05-04 to 1872-05-31; KG11365.394 (Box 10)
  Also identified as: Vol. 4.
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1872-05-31 to 1872-06-10; KG11365.395 (Box 10)
  Also identified as: Vol. 5.
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1872-06-10 to 1872-06-30; KG11365.396 (Box 10)
  Also identified as: Vol. 6.
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1872-06-30 to 1872-07-30; KG11365.397 (Box 10)
  Also identified as: Vol. 7.
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1872-07-30 to 1872-08-09; KG11365.398 (Box 10)
  Also identified as: Vol. 8.
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1872-08-09 to 1872-08-18; KG11365.399 (Box 10)
  Also identified as: Vol. 9.
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1872-08-18 to 1873-03-09; KG11365.400 (Box 11)
  Also identified as: Vol. 10.
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1873-03-09 to 1873-06-08; KG11365.401 (Box 11)
  Also identified as: Vol. 11.
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1873-06-08 to 1873-09-06; KG11365.402 (Box 11)
  Also identified as: Vol. 12.
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1873-09-06 to 1873-09-22; KG11365.403 (Box 11)
  Also identified as: Vol. 13.
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1873-09-22 to 1873-09-30; KG11365.404 (Box 11)
  Also identified as: Vol. 14.
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1873-09-30 to 1873-10-11; KG11365.405 (Box 11)
  Also identified as: Vol. 15.
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1873-10-11 to 1874-04-13; KG11365.406 (Box 11)
  Also identified as: Vol. 16.
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1874-04-13 to 1874-05-20; KG11365.407 (Box 11)
  Also identified as: Vol. 18.
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1874-05-20 to 1874-07-17; KG11365.408 (Box 11)
  Also identified as: Vol. 19.
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1874-07-17 to 1874-08-03; KG11365.409 (Box 11)
  Also identified as: Vol. 20.
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1874-08-03 to 1874-08-22; KG11365.410 (Box 11)
  Also identified as: Vol. 21.
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1874-08-22 to 1874-11-26; KG11365.411 (Box 11)
  Also identified as: Vol. 22.
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1874-11-26 to 1874-12-21; KG11365.412 (Box 11)
  Also identified as: Vol. 23.
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1874-12-21 to 1875-01-14; KG11365.413 (Box 11)
  Also identified as: Vol. 24.
- Record of Photometric Observations, 1872-05-28; KG11365.414 (Box 11)
  Also identified as: Vol. 25.
- Index to books on Meridian Circle Work, 1870 to 1886; KG11365.415 (Box 11)
- Fundamental Stars for zones, 1873-03-17 to 1873-12-01; KG11365.416 (Box 11)
- General Catalog Observations and Reductions, 1871 to 1872; KG11365.417 (Box 11)
- Fundamental Star Observations and Reductions, Final Values, 1870 to 1871; KG11365.418 (Box 11)
- Mars, Mars Companion Stars, ARIADNE Companion Stars, 1877; KG11365.419 (Box 11)
- Flexure Constants, Equator Point Corrections, 1874 to 1875; KG11365.420 (Box 11)
- Instrumental Constants 1870-71, depending on new Pulkowa Places, KG11365.421 (Box 11)
- Barometer, Thermometer Runs. Collimations, Flexure, 1870 to 1879; KG11365.422 (Box 11)
- Refraction Constants, 1870 to 1886; KG11365.423 (Box 11)
- Observations with Meridian Circle on Zones 50 to 55, 1870-11-16 to 1870-12-16; KG11365.424 (Box 11)
- Observations with Meridian Circle on Zones 50 to 55, 1870-12-16 to 1871-03-28; KG11365.425 (Box 11)
- Miscellaneous Tables Formulae for Zone Reductions, 1870 to 1871; KG11365.426 (Box 11)
- Miscellaneous Observations Transit of Venus Longitude Montreal - Cambridge, 1883 to 1887; KG11365.427 (Box 11)
- Observations of Tempel's Comet 1873, Asteroids 1873, Periodicity of Ruling Machine Screw, KG11365.428 (Box 11)
- Ruling Machine Screws; Discovery of Asteroids 112 and 109 & Ephemerides, KG11365.429 (Box 11)
- Asteroid 109 - Elements and Ephemerides, 1877 to 1878; KG11365.430 (Box 11)
- Orbit of Asteroids 109 and 112, 1871 to 1874; KG11365.431 (Box 11)
- [Orbits of asteroid] 112, KG11365.432 (Box 11)
- Planetary Positions (Heliocentric), 1750 to 1860; KG11365.433 (Box 11)
- Star Lists (Zones), 1871; KG11365.434 (Box 11)
- Chronograph Record, 1880-05-27 to 1880-10-05; KG11365.435 (Box 11)
- Absolute work Star List - Final list of dates of observations, 1879 to 1881; KG11365.436 (Box 11)
  John A. Dunne.
- Absolute work Meridian Circle observations, 1879 to 1881; KG11365.437 (Box 12)
  Anna Winlock.
- Absolute Work Notebook, 1898 to 1907; KG11365.438 (Box 12)
  Selina C. Bond.
- Posting Book, 1897 to 1908; KG11365.439 (Box 12)
- Roger's Aboslute work notebook, 1904 to 1911; KG11365.440 (Box 12)
- Special Light Curves with Photometer, 1895 to 1896; KG11365.441 (Box 12)
- Variable Stars, 1897; KG11365.442 (Box 12)
- Ephemerides of variable stars, 1896 to 1898; KG11365.443 (Box 12)
- Measurement of Comp. Stars for variable with photometer, 1895 to 1901; KG11365.444 (Box 12)
- [Variable Stars], 1897 to 1898; KG11365.445 (Box 12)
- Observations of Variable Stars, 1890 to 1891; KG11365.446 (Box 12)
  Also identified as: I.
  Maxwell Reed.
- Observations of Variable Stars, 1891; KG11365.447 (Box 12)
  Also identified as: II.
- Observations of Variable Stars, 1891 to 1892; KG11365.448 (Box 12)
  Also identified as: III.
- Observations of Variable Stars, 1892; KG11365.449 (Box 12)
  Also identified as: IV.
- Observations of Variable Stars, 1892 to 1893; KG11365.450 (Box 12)
  Also identified as: V.
- Observations of Variable Stars, 1894 to 1895; KG11365.451 (Box 12)
  Also identified as: VII.
- Observations of Variable Stars, 1893 to 1894; KG11365.452 (Box 12)
  Also identified as: VI.
- Observations of Variable Stars, 1896 to 1896; KG11365.453 (Box 12)
  Also identified as: VIII.
- Observations of Variable Stars, 1898 to 1990; KG11365.454 (Box 12)
  Also identified as: IX.
- Observations of Variable Stars, 1900; KG11365.455 (Box 12)
- Notebook of Visual Observations, 1899 to 1902; KG11365.456 (Box 12)
  H.R. Colson.
- West Equatorial Observations, 1898-04-10 to 1899-05-12; KG11365.457 (Box 12)
- Equatorial Work [record of 72 books], KG11365.458 (Box 13)
  Also identified as: [R14].
- Index - also lists of Variables, etc., KG11365.459 (Box 13)
  Also identified as: [R15].
- Index, KG11365.460 (Box 13)
  Also identified as: [R16].
- Rutherford Millimeter Plate Measurements, 1897-08-16 to 1882-07-25; KG11365.461 (Box 13)
  Also identified as: R17.
- Meteorological Observations, etc., 1880-06-23 to 1885-08-20; KG11365.462 (Box 13)
  Also identified as: R18.
- [Observations] Aug-Sept 1877, 1877-08-01 to 1877-09-01; KG11365.463 (Box 13)
  Also identified as: R19.
- [Observations] Aug-Oct 1877, 1877-08-01 to 1877-09-01; KG11365.464 (Box 13)
  Also identified as: R20.
- Omicron Ceti, lambda Cygnus, S_____, beta Persei, 1838 to 1854; KG11365.465 (Box 13)
  Also identified as: R22.
  See KG11366.868 for R21.
- [Observations] 1877-1879, 1877 to 1879; KG11365.466 (Box 13)
  Also identified as: R23.
- Photometer Reductions, 1877; KG11365.467 (Box 13)
  Also identified as: R24.
- Ephemerides of Saturn's and Jupiter's satellites, KG11365.468 (Box 13)
  Also identified as: R25.
- Errors of Circles, Miscellaneous Observations, West Equatorial, 1877 to 1878; KG11365.469 (Box 13)
  Also identified as: R26.
- Miscellaneous Observations and Reductions, 1878; KG11365.470 (Box 13)
  Also identified as: R28.
- [Summary of Variable Stars], 1840 to 1862; KG11365.471 (Box 13)
  Also identified as: R29.
- Photometric Observations, 1877; KG11365.472 (Box 13)
  Also identified as: R30.
- Photometric Observations, 1878; KG11365.473 (Box 13)
  Also identified as: R31.
- [Observations] c 1878, KG11365.474 (Box 13)
  Also identified as: R32.
- Observations and lists, 1879 to 1881; KG11365.475 (Box 13)
  Also identified as: R33.
  Edward C. Pickering.
- Form for Equatorial Observations, 1879; KG11365.476 (Box 13)
  Also identified as: R34.
- Prospective work and proposed form of publication - W. Equatorial, 1874 to 1881; KG11365.477 (Box 13)
  Also identified as: R35.
- [Observations] 1878, KG11365.478 (Box 13)
  Also identified as: R43.
- [Observations] 1878, KG11365.479 (Box 13)
  Also identified as: R44.
- [Observations] 1879, KG11365.480 (Box 14)
  Also identified as: R45.
- Photometric Observations with West Equatorial, 1878 to 1879; KG11365.481 (Box 14)
  Also identified as: R46.
- Photometric Observations with West Equatorial, 1878 to 1879; KG11365.482 (Box 14)
- Description of Procedures and Optical Setups, KG11365.483 (Box 14)
- Description of Procedures and Other Observations, 1879; KG11365.484 (Box 14)
- Description of Procedures and Other Observations, 1879 to 1880; KG11365.485 (Box 14)
- Description of Procedures and Other Observations, 1879; KG11365.486 (Box 14)
- Description of Procedures and Other Observations, Planetoids and Planets, 1879 to 1880; KG11365.487 (Box 14)
- Eclipses of Jupiter Satellites, 1878 to 1879; KG11365.488 (Box 14)
- Eye and Photon Estimates of Standard Maps, 1881; KG11365.489 (Box 14)
  J.R. Edward.
- Comet Reductions #1, 1881; KG11365.490 (Box 14)
- Comet Reductions #2, 1880 to 1883; KG11365.491 (Box 14)
- [Comets] 26, 1881 to 1882; KG11365.492 (Box 14)
- [Comets] 28, 1882; KG11365.493 (Box 14)
- 6.25-inch, 1882 to 1883; KG11365.494 (Box 14)
- 15-inch, 1884; KG11365.495 (Box 14)
- Comets, 1882 to 1888; KG11365.496 (Box 14)
- Comets, 1882 to 1885; KG11365.497 (Box 14)
- Comets, 1883 to 1887; KG11365.498 (Box 14)
- 15-inch Equatorial, 1885; KG11365.499 (Box 14)
- Comets, 1882 to 1889; KG11365.500 (Box 14)
- Comets, 1882 to 1894; KG11365.501 (Box 14)
- Comets, 1883 to 1887; KG11365.502 (Box 15)
- Comets, 1885 to 1888; KG11365.503 (Box 15)
- Comets, 1888 to 1889; KG11365.504 (Box 15)
- Comets copies of telegrams, 1889 to 1898; KG11365.505 (Box 15)
- Comets (10), 1890; KG11365.506 (Box 15)
- Comets (9), 1889 to 1890; KG11365.507 (Box 15)
- Journal (Construction of Dome, etc.), 1889 to 1891; KG11365.508 (Box 15)
  R.W.Clifford.
- [Observations] 55, 1890; KG11365.509 (Box 15)
- [Observations] 59, 1891; KG11365.510 (Box 15)
- Gigenschein & Zodiacal Light Observations, 1891 to 1892; KG11365.511 (Box 15)
- Comets, 1891 to 1892; KG11365.512 (Box 15)
- Journal (Arequipa), 1891 to 1894; KG11365.513 (Box 15)
  Andrew E. Douglas.
- [Observations] 62, 1892; KG11365.514 (Box 15)